[{
  "prompt": "After asking many random people if they have 2 children and also if one is a boy born on a Tuesday, someone answers yes. What is the probability (as an improper fraction) that this person has 2 boys? Assume an equal chance of giving birth to either sex and an equal chance to giving birth on any day.",
  "answer": "13/27",
  "level": 5
},
{
  "prompt": "I want to weigh 10 people. What is the minimum number of times I must use the scale?",
  "answer": "1",
  "level": 5
},
{
  "prompt": "You drive to the store at 20 mph and return by the same route at 30 mph. Not including the time spent shopping, what was your average speed in miles per hour?",
  "answer": "24",
  "level": 1
},
{
  "prompt": "There are several chickens and rabbits at a farm (with no other types of animals). There are 72 heads and 200 feet at the farm. How many chickens are there?",
  "answer": "44",
  "level": 2
},
{
  "prompt": "There are several chickens and rabbits at a farm (with no other types of animals). There are 72 heads and 200 feet at the farm. How many rabbits are there?",
  "answer": "28",
  "level": 2
},
{
  "prompt": "At a restaurant, you can order chicken strips in small (6), large (9) and family-size (20). What is the largest number of strips that it is not possible to obtain by purchasing some combination of boxes?",
  "answer": "43",
  "level": 2
},
{
  "prompt": "You can paddle your canoe 7mph through any placid lake. The stream flows at 3mph. The moment you start to paddle up stream a fisherman looses one of his bobbers in the water fourteen miles up stream of you. How many hours does it take for you and the bobber to meet?",
  "answer": "2",
  "level": 2
},
{
  "prompt": "Cathy has twelve black socks and twelve white socks in her drawer. In complete darkness, and without looking, how many socks must she take from the drawer in order to be sure to get a pair that match?",
  "answer": "3",
  "level": 2
},
{
  "prompt": "Mary's mum has four children. The first child is named April. The second May. The third June. What is the name of the fourth child?",
  "answer": "Mary",
  "level": 2
},
{
  "prompt": "A man has $1.15 in six coins. He can't make change for a dollar, a half dollar, a quarter, a dime, or a nickel. How many dimes did he have?",
  "answer": "4",
  "level": 5
},
{
  "prompt": "A group of sheep and chickens have a total of 99 heads and feet. There are twice as many chickens as sheep. How many of sheep are there?",
  "answer": "9",
  "level": 5
},
{
  "prompt": "If a boy and a half can eat a hot dog and a half in a minute and a half, how many hot dogs can six boys eat in six minutes?",
  "answer": "24",
  "level": 5
}]
